ANYA POPOVA

Junior Back - end developer with Java

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Junior Back-end developer currently looking for a new opportunity. I decided to change my carreer path after 10+ years of working in the field of architecture and interior design. As a result of my professional experience I am skilled in coordination, communication, managing projects and working in a team. I am a hardworking and dedicated person who likes to experiment and find the most efficient ways of making things work. I am eager to join a team and contribute to the development of awesome applications so I am looking for a Junior Back-end Developer position.

EDUCATION



2022

Ironhack Barcelona

Java Back-end bootcamp



2021

SkillFactory

Data Analysis with Python course



2019

GeekBrains onlline school

Python course

Tage
Instituto de
arquitectura
avanzada de

2011-2012

Institute for Advanced Architecture of

Catalonia

Master in Advanced Architecture



2005-2011

Moscow Institute of Architecture

Bachelor of Arts in Architecture

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



2021-2022

Lázaro Rosa-Violán studio

Architect

Intercon® 2(

2017-2020

Intercon

Team leader



2015-2017

FabLab Bcn

Lab operator

Tage
Instituto de arquitectura

2013-2015

Institute for Advanced Architecture of Catalonia

Digital Fabrication tutor



LANGUAGES

- Russian
- English
- Spanish
- Catalan

TECHNICAL SKILLS



Java



Spring



Maven



RESTful APIs



MySQL



Python



Git

JS

Javascript basics



HTML + CSS basics

OTHER SKILLS

- Drawing
- Translation
- Communication
- Team management
- Project management
- Problem solving

Phone: 652687498

Email:

anya.chocolat@gmail.com

LinkedIn: bit.ly/AnyaLinkedIn

GitHub:

github.com/anya-chocolat